<schemalist>
  <schema id="com.canonical.indicator.sound" path="/com/canonical/indicator/sound/" gettext-domain="indicator-sound">
    <key name="blacklisted-media-players" type="as">
      <summary>A list of applications blacklisted from the sound menu</summary>
      <default>[]</default>
      <description>
        Each media player which abides by the MPRIS2 spec will automatically appear in the menu.
        This array should contain the desktop file names (minus .desktop suffix) of applications which
        do not want to be included in the sound menu.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="interested-media-players" type="as">
      <summary>A list of applications which at some point have registered with the sound menu</summary>
      <default>[]</default>
      <description>
        Each media player which abides by the MPRIS2 spec will automatically appear in the menu.
        This array should contain the desktop file names (minus .desktop suffix) of applications which
        have at some point appeared in the menU. This allows the menu remember and display offlined applications.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="preferred-media-players" type="as">
      <summary>A list of applications that will have player controls visible all the time</summary>
      <default>[ 'rhythmbox' ]</default>
      <description>
        A list of applications that will have player controls visible all the time
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="global-mute" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Initial setting for global mute (mute all) on the menu </summary>
      <description>
        On start up volume should not be muted.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="show-notify-osd-on-scroll" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Initial setting for showing notify-osd notification on scroll volume-change</summary>
      <description>
        When using the mouse scroll-wheel over the indicator-sound icon, the volume changes.
        Enabling this setting, every scroll volume-change a notify-osd bubble with the
        updated volume value will be shown (if supported by your notification daemon).
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="visible" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Whether or not to show the sound indicator in the menu bar.</summary>
      <description>
        Whether or not to show the sound indicator in the menu bar.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="greeter-export" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Whether or not to export the currently playing song to the greeter.</summary>
      <description>
        If enabled the sound indicator will export the current player and
        song to the greeter so that it can be shown if the user is selected
        and the sound menu is shown.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
