<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE refentry PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN"
        "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd">

<refentry id="plymouth">

        <refentryinfo>
                <title>plymouth</title>
                <productname>plymouth</productname>

                <authorgroup>
                        <author>
                                <contrib>Developer</contrib>
                                <firstname>Kristian</firstname>
                                <surname>Høgsberg</surname>
                        </author>
                        <author>
                                <contrib>Developer</contrib>
                                <firstname>Ray</firstname>
                                <surname>Strode</surname>
                        </author>
                </authorgroup>

        </refentryinfo>

        <refmeta>
                <refentrytitle>plymouth</refentrytitle>
                <manvolnum>8</manvolnum>
                <refmiscinfo class="manual">System Administration</refmiscinfo>
        </refmeta>

        <refnamediv>
                <refname>plymouth</refname>
                <refpurpose>A graphical boot system and logger</refpurpose>
        </refnamediv>

        <refsect1>
                <title>Description</title>

<para>
<command>plymouth</command> is a graphical boot system for Linux which takes advantage of
the kernel-based mode setting (KMS) available for modern graphic  cards
to  provide  a  seamless,  flickerfree  and  attractive boot screen. It
allows to choose between various, static or animated  graphical  themes
to  spruce  up  the  startup  and avoid the noise generated by the vast
amount of kernel messages while the machine boots into X.   On  systems
where  kernel-based  mode setting is not available, plymouth falls back
to a text mode boot screen which provides a simple progress bar to pro‐
vide feedback during boot.
</para>
<para>
In order for the configured default plymouth theme to be loaded during
boot, the option `splash' (or `rhgb' for  backward  compatibility  with
the RHGB  boot  splash) must be provided at the kernel command line.
Without this command line option, plymouth will default to showing
detailed boot output.
</para>

<para>
During the boot process, the user can switch between the graphical theme
and the detailed boot output using the Escape key.
</para>

        </refsect1>

        <refsect1>
                <title>See Also</title>
                <para>
                        <citerefentry><refentrytitle>grub</refentrytitle><manvolnum>8</manvolnum></citerefentry>,
                        <citerefentry><refentrytitle>plymouth-set-theme</refentrytitle><manvolnum>1</manvolnum></citerefentry>,
                        <citerefentry><refentrytitle>plymouthd</refentrytitle><manvolnum>8</manvolnum></citerefentry>,
                        <citerefentry><refentrytitle>plymouth</refentrytitle><manvolnum>1</manvolnum></citerefentry>,
                        <ulink url="http://www.freedesktop.org/wiki/Software/Plymouth">http://www.freedesktop.org/wiki/Software/Plymouth</ulink>
                </para>
        </refsect1>

        <refsect1>
                <title>Authors</title>
                <para>
plymouth  was  originally  prototyped  and  named  by Kristian Høgsberg,
originally written by Ray Strode and has had significant contributions from
Charlie Brej. It has also had contributions from Peter Jones, Adam Jackson,
Frederic Crozat and others.
                </para>
        </refsect1>
</refentry>
